<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Red Ruth on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/red-ruth/</link><description>Recent content in Red Ruth on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 21:25:09 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/red-ruth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>collecting blood for fun and profit</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/28/collecting-blood-for-fun-and-profit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 23:22:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/28/collecting-blood-for-fun-and-profit/</guid><description>Horns grows a pair of wings, and Cassandra agrees to help the party in exchange for the &lt;em>bag of devouring.&lt;/em> A tortle named Krull escorts the Menagerie from Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower to Arkhan himself. They negotiate a trade of the &lt;em>orb of dragonkind&lt;/em> for a vial of Tiamat&amp;rsquo;s blood and Val backs down from dueling Arkhan. Uldrak&amp;rsquo;s empyrean form is restored, and on the way back to the Demon Zapper the party stops at a conveniently-relocated Wandering Emporium to shelter from an acid storm.</description></item><item><title>stack.push(quest)</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/14/stack-push-quest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 09:19:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/14/stack-push-quest/</guid><description>Red Ruth tells the party that Ralzala can be freed by drinking the blood of a titan, and conveniently also divulges the location of a titan named Uldrak. The Menagerie names their infernal warmachine &amp;ldquo;the Anti-Chrysler&amp;rdquo; and goes to pay Uldrak a visit, but they&amp;rsquo;re diverted yet again by the need to restore his titan form. They set course for Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower, and are attacked by vrocks along the way.</description></item><item><title>friendly fire</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/08/friendly-fire/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/08/friendly-fire/</guid><description>The Menagerie set up camp in Red Ruth&amp;rsquo;s yard to house-sit while she&amp;rsquo;s away. In the middle of resting, they&amp;rsquo;re attacked by banshees and a treant! Gimble learns a little about arcane edge cases, Not-Bailey dies for a moment, Horns becomes a fire elemental, and Finn feeds the treant to a bag.</description></item><item><title>avernian errands</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/31/avernian-errands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/31/avernian-errands/</guid><description>The Menagerie meet Red Ruth and she tells them her price for the information about Ralzala that they want. They Tokyo-drift through the lava geysers of the fire plains and arrive at the Wandering Emporium to book Red Ruth&amp;rsquo;s spa visit. While at the Wandering Emporium, Horns has a beer and the crew do a small amount of shopping before racing back across the fire plains to house-sit for Red Ruth while she takes herself out for a spa day.</description></item><item><title>hashtag not all bags</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/25/hashtag-not-all-bags/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/25/hashtag-not-all-bags/</guid><description>Lulu remembers some locations that may help the party find Zariel&amp;rsquo;s ring, and the group travels to a weapon known as the Demon Zapper. They meet Ralzala, a dao who guards the Demon Zapper, and undertake a quest to find Red Ruth in the Bone Brambles for information on Ralzala&amp;rsquo;s behalf. Oneshoe almost gets eaten by a malevolent purse.</description></item><item><title>Red Ruth</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/red-ruth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/red-ruth/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography A hag who lives in the Bone Brambles, a region in Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>The Bone Brambles</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/locations/the-bone-brambles/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/locations/the-bone-brambles/</guid><description>Map Key Info A region of Avernus, the first layer of the Nine Hells of Baator. Home of the hag Red Ruth.</description></item></channel></rss>