<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Wolves on tlake.io</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/the-wolves/</link><description>Recent content in The Wolves on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><atom:link href="http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/the-wolves/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Walk Without Shame</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/30/the-walk-without-shame/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/30/the-walk-without-shame/</guid><description>The party continues processing the results of their research requests, an unsteady Gimble has some troubling revelations at the Temple of Oghma, and Oneshoe enthusiastically takes one for the team. Just as the party considers leaving to find Nyx, they are granted access to The Emerald Door and the interior of Candlekeep.</description></item><item><title>The Wolves</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/the-wolves/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/the-wolves/</guid><description>Description An organization of operatives from Gray&amp;rsquo;s past, ostensibly headquartered on an island called Marea.
Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Research Obstructing Research</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/02/research-obstructing-research/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/02/research-obstructing-research/</guid><description>Gimble&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em>contact other plane&lt;/em> goes a little off the rails, and he has a conversation with Gruumsh. The group try to come up with a new plan for dealing with Nyx&amp;rsquo;s pursuers, since their charade in Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate failed to pull them off of Nyx&amp;rsquo;s trail. Val tours the Court of Air looking for any possible way to get past the Emerald Door. Cassandra visits, and the first round of requested knowledge is delievered.</description></item><item><title>Can I Get a Receipt?</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/06/07/can-i-get-a-receipt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/06/07/can-i-get-a-receipt/</guid><description>Gimble fails to scry upon his pursuer, yet the party pushes on and teleports to Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate, where they make some noise about researching The Shard of Mystra. Horns enhances his wildshape ability, and Zed continues to evangelize the way of yoga. After the brief stop, they &lt;em>wind walk&lt;/em> the remainder of their journey, alighting just outside the fortress of Candlekeep.</description></item><item><title>A Study in Synthwave</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</guid><description>Psithyron displays his latest masterpiece. Gray opens up more about his family. A desperate message from Finn is foreseen, and a gnome returns. The party considers their options, and a bold, but likely foolish plan is made.</description></item></channel></rss>