<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Uldrak on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/uldrak/</link><description>Recent content in Uldrak on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 01:08:56 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/uldrak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>collecting blood for fun and profit</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/28/collecting-blood-for-fun-and-profit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 23:22:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/28/collecting-blood-for-fun-and-profit/</guid><description>Horns grows a pair of wings, and Cassandra agrees to help the party in exchange for the &lt;em>bag of devouring.&lt;/em> A tortle named Krull escorts the Menagerie from Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower to Arkhan himself. They negotiate a trade of the &lt;em>orb of dragonkind&lt;/em> for a vial of Tiamat&amp;rsquo;s blood and Val backs down from dueling Arkhan. Uldrak&amp;rsquo;s empyrean form is restored, and on the way back to the Demon Zapper the party stops at a conveniently-relocated Wandering Emporium to shelter from an acid storm.</description></item><item><title>stack.push(quest)</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/14/stack-push-quest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 09:19:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/14/stack-push-quest/</guid><description>Red Ruth tells the party that Ralzala can be freed by drinking the blood of a titan, and conveniently also divulges the location of a titan named Uldrak. The Menagerie names their infernal warmachine &amp;ldquo;the Anti-Chrysler&amp;rdquo; and goes to pay Uldrak a visit, but they&amp;rsquo;re diverted yet again by the need to restore his titan form. They set course for Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower, and are attacked by vrocks along the way.</description></item><item><title>Uldrak</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/uldrak/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/uldrak/</guid><description>Description Appearance Image property of Wizards of the Coast LLC.
Personality Biography The empyrean Uldrak quested into the Nine Hells to slay Tiamat and win glory for his deity, Surtur, but he was beaten handily by the dragon queen.</description></item></channel></rss>