<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Avernus on tlake.io</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/locations/avernus/</link><description>Recent content in Avernus on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><atom:link href="http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/locations/avernus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Graz'zt</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/grazzt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 17:09:11 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/grazzt/</guid><description/></item><item><title>2022 06 08</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/06/08/2022-06-08/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 23:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/06/08/2022-06-08/</guid><description>Now that Horns has been exonerated, the party prepares to leave the Hells, but a certain demon prince has other plans.</description></item><item><title>collecting blood for fun and profit</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/28/collecting-blood-for-fun-and-profit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 23:22:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/28/collecting-blood-for-fun-and-profit/</guid><description>Horns grows a pair of wings, and Cassandra agrees to help the party in exchange for the &lt;em>bag of devouring.&lt;/em> A tortle named Krull escorts the Menagerie from Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower to Arkhan himself. They negotiate a trade of the &lt;em>orb of dragonkind&lt;/em> for a vial of Tiamat&amp;rsquo;s blood and Val backs down from dueling Arkhan. Uldrak&amp;rsquo;s empyrean form is restored, and on the way back to the Demon Zapper the party stops at a conveniently-relocated Wandering Emporium to shelter from an acid storm.</description></item><item><title>Krull</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/krull/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/krull/</guid><description>Description Appearance A male tortle.
Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>of motorcycles and newtonian physics</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/22/of-motorcycles-and-newtonian-physics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 09:19:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/22/of-motorcycles-and-newtonian-physics/</guid><description>The Menagerie approach Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower and, upon seeing it guarded by a dragon, decide to recuperate and gather their strength instead of rushing in. Gimble casts &lt;em>identify&lt;/em> on the &lt;em>orb of dragonkind.&lt;/em> Gray is paid a visit by the Raven Queen who delivers an intercepted letter and a warning against the Feywild. A devilish warband starts a fight, and the party makes a new drow acquaintance.</description></item><item><title>Cassandra Belacourt</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/cassandra-belacourt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/cassandra-belacourt/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Cassandra Belacourt Agent of The Reclamation &amp;ndash; a party which seeks to reclaim artifacts that should not be out in the wild.
Description Appearance A female drow.</description></item><item><title>stack.push(quest)</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/14/stack-push-quest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 09:19:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/14/stack-push-quest/</guid><description>Red Ruth tells the party that Ralzala can be freed by drinking the blood of a titan, and conveniently also divulges the location of a titan named Uldrak. The Menagerie names their infernal warmachine &amp;ldquo;the Anti-Chrysler&amp;rdquo; and goes to pay Uldrak a visit, but they&amp;rsquo;re diverted yet again by the need to restore his titan form. They set course for Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower, and are attacked by vrocks along the way.</description></item><item><title>Arkhan</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/arkhan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/arkhan/</guid><description>Description A male red chromatic dragonborn.
Appearance Personality Biography A devout follower of Tiamat, he maintains a tower on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Arkhan's Tower</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/arkhans-tower/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/arkhans-tower/</guid><description>Map Key Info An obelisk capped with five large spikes, defended by obsidian ramparts and several patrolling dragons.
Location Avernus, in the Nine Hells of Baator.
Residents Arkhan the Cruel</description></item><item><title>Tiamat</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/tiamat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/tiamat/</guid><description>Description Appearance A gargantuan five-headed dragon, each head being one of the five types of chromatic dragons.
Personality Biography The (evil) Queen of (chromatic) Dragons, Tiamat is imprisoned somewhere on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator.</description></item><item><title>Uldrak</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/uldrak/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/uldrak/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography The empyrean Uldrak quested into the Nine Hells to slay Tiamat and win glory for his deity, Surtur, but he was beaten handily by the dragon queen.</description></item><item><title>friendly fire</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/08/friendly-fire/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/08/friendly-fire/</guid><description>The Menagerie set up camp in Red Ruth&amp;rsquo;s yard to house-sit while she&amp;rsquo;s away. In the middle of resting, they&amp;rsquo;re attacked by banshees and a treant! Gimble learns a little about arcane edge cases, Not-Bailey dies for a moment, Horns becomes a fire elemental, and Finn feeds the treant to a bag.</description></item><item><title>avernian errands</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/31/avernian-errands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/31/avernian-errands/</guid><description>The Menagerie meet Red Ruth and she tells them her price for the information about Ralzala that they want. They Tokyo-drift through the lava geysers of the fire plains and arrive at the Wandering Emporium to book Red Ruth&amp;rsquo;s spa visit. While at the Wandering Emporium, Horns has a beer and the crew do a small amount of shopping before racing back across the fire plains to house-sit for Red Ruth while she takes herself out for a spa day.</description></item><item><title>Fort Knucklebone</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/fort-knucklebone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/fort-knucklebone/</guid><description>Map Key Info A fortified outpost on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator. Ruled by Mad Maggie</description></item><item><title>Mad Maggie</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/mad-maggie/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/mad-maggie/</guid><description>Description A female night hag.
Appearance Personality Biography Head honcho of Fort Knucklebones, a fortified outpost on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Mahadi</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/mahadi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/mahadi/</guid><description>Description A male rakshasa.
Appearance Personality Biography Owner of the Wandering Emporium (commonly found somewhere on the layer Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator), and proprietor of Infernal Rapture.</description></item><item><title>The Wandering Emporium</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/the-wandering-emporium/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/the-wandering-emporium/</guid><description>Key Info “All are welcome here. No fighting! No spellcasting! No exceptions!”
― sign at the entrance of the Wandering Emporium
Owner Mahadi is the master of the Wandering Emporium and proprietor of the Infernal Rapture.</description></item><item><title>Bel</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/bel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/bel/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography Unwilling advisor and second-in-command to Zariel on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>hashtag not all bags</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/25/hashtag-not-all-bags/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/25/hashtag-not-all-bags/</guid><description>Lulu remembers some locations that may help the party find Zariel&amp;rsquo;s ring, and the group travels to a weapon known as the Demon Zapper. They meet Ralzala, a dao who guards the Demon Zapper, and undertake a quest to find Red Ruth in the Bone Brambles for information on Ralzala&amp;rsquo;s behalf. Oneshoe almost gets eaten by a malevolent purse.</description></item><item><title>Ralzala</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/ralzala/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/ralzala/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography A dao who was responsible for guarding the Demon Zapper on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Red Ruth</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/red-ruth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/red-ruth/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography A hag who lives in the Bone Brambles, a region in Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>"zed's folly"</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/10/zeds-folly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/10/zeds-folly/</guid><description>The consequences of Horns&amp;rsquo; and Zed&amp;rsquo;s actions result in a confrontation against an opponent capable of dropping Zed. The Menagerie save Lulu from being hollyphantnapped by a hellwasp.</description></item><item><title>Avernus</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/avernus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/avernus/</guid><description>Map Key Info</description></item><item><title>Haruman</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/haruman/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/haruman/</guid><description>Description A narzugon that the Menagerie encountered in Avernus, the first layer of the Nine Hells of Baator.
Appearance Personality Biography He had been one of Zariel&amp;rsquo;s generals in the time before her fall, and when her host crashed and broke upon the infernal legions, Haruman took it upon himself to deliver judgement upon those of the host who deserted the cause.</description></item><item><title>Lulu</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/lulu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/lulu/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography A tiny hollyphant that the party met while on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator who once was a longtime friend and ally to Zariel before her fall.</description></item><item><title>The Nine Hells of Baator</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/the-nine-hells-of-baator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/the-nine-hells-of-baator/</guid><description>Map Key Info A lawful evil plane containing nine separate layers of torment:
Avernus Dis Minauros Phlegethos Stygia Malbolge Maladomini Cania Nessus</description></item><item><title>Zariel</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zariel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zariel/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography The archduchess of Avernus, first layer of the Nine Hells of Baator.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item></channel></rss>