<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kellis MacCleod on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/kellis-maccleod/</link><description>Recent content in Kellis MacCleod on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:47:53 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/kellis-maccleod/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Playing Chicken With a Dragon</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2025/05/28/playing-chicken-with-a-dragon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2025/05/28/playing-chicken-with-a-dragon/</guid><description>The Menagerie windwalk in search of the ancient white dragon that once had been a snow-covered hill. They&amp;rsquo;re successful in tracking it down, and talk it into landing. The party is split between trying to fight the dragon and trying to lie to the dragon, and eventually Gray is able to use the Heart of Winter to convince the dragon that they&amp;rsquo;re here at the behest of the Queen of Air and Darkness. They manage to convince the dragon to hand over the frozen form of Kellis and barely avoid being conscripted into whatever the dragon&amp;rsquo;s current purpose is, and it flies away to resume its quest. As the Menagerie begin the long trek back to the copse of trees, the dragon turns around and flies directly towards the party as a trio of nautiloid ships appear out of nowhere, as if dropping out of warp.</description></item><item><title>Somebody Order a Blizzard?</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024/09/18/somebody-order-a-blizzard/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024/09/18/somebody-order-a-blizzard/</guid><description>The Menagerie</description></item><item><title>Kellis MacCleod</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/kellis-maccleod/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/kellis-maccleod/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Kellis MacCleod One of two owners and proprietors of MacCleod&amp;rsquo;s, a well-respected tavern. Kellis tends to focus more on the acquisition of product and the distillation of moonshine, a liquor made from the actual light of the moon.</description></item></channel></rss>