<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Nine Hells of Baator on tlake.io</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/locations/the-nine-hells-of-baator/</link><description>Recent content in The Nine Hells of Baator on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><atom:link href="http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/locations/the-nine-hells-of-baator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Levistus</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/levistus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/levistus/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Graz'zt</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/grazzt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 17:09:11 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/grazzt/</guid><description/></item><item><title>2022 03 30</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/03/30/2022-03-30/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/03/30/2022-03-30/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary The party&amp;rsquo;s escape from the tower stalls with the realization that they are unable to teleport all of their summoned creatures to safety. Knowing Fierna could locate them any moment, some hard decisions are made at the expense of Zed&amp;rsquo;s minotaur friends, and the Menagerie finally teleports away.</description></item><item><title>2022 03 16</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/03/16/2022-03-16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/03/16/2022-03-16/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary Having dispatched the remaining guards in the corridor, the party resumes its search for Magrin. They find a room with six pillars, adorned with piles of teeth&amp;ndash;apparently some ghastly connection to Gelfondi&amp;rsquo;s machine room found earlier.</description></item><item><title>2022 02 16</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/16/2022-02-16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/16/2022-02-16/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary Alone and defiant, Finn squares up against the incoming bone devil and its guard. She is swiftly restrained by a chain devil, and Finn summons her signature flumphs in retribution, but this does not stop the bone devil from savagely attacking Finn with its claws and hideous stinger.</description></item><item><title>2022 02 02</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/02/2022-02-02/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/02/2022-02-02/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary The party carefully creeps along the southern corridor towards the west, hoping to avoid further detection. At the sight of a bone devil ahead, Zed and his minotaurs instead choose to (somehow) squeeze into a small alcove towards the center of the tower, where they uncover two hidden imps keeping watch.</description></item><item><title>Gelfondi</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/gelfondi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/gelfondi/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Gelfondi The devil in charge of the operations on the 42nd floor of Fierna&amp;rsquo;s tower.
Description Appearance Gelfondi is a horned devil, slightly shorter than usual. He was wearing some type or robes when the party surprised him in 2022-02-02 Import Campaign.</description></item><item><title>2022 01 19</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/19/2022-01-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/19/2022-01-19/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary The party desperately tries to dispatch the the two horned devils and subordinate in the main corridor before the devils can alert the guard barracks and the rest of the tower.</description></item><item><title>Aeortis</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/aeortis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/aeortis/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Aeortis An apparent young girl who designed much Fierna&amp;rsquo;s tower.
Description Appearance a (supposed) young girl, accompanied by three hellhounds Personality Biography Relationships Oneshoe In payment for giving information to the party, Aeortis required the party to perform a service for her and retrieve a particular soul coin from Fierna&amp;rsquo;s tower.</description></item><item><title>Belial</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/belial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/belial/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Belial Belial is the lord of Phlegethos, who jointly rules the fourth layer together with his daughter Fierna. This unusual partnership was allowed by Asmodeus as an exception to the usual requirement of one ruler per layer.</description></item><item><title>Carmen</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/carmen/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/carmen/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Carmen Known as one of the most powerful and effective lawyers in Phlegethos.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Due to her extraordinary reputation, Carmen commands exceedingly high fees for her services.</description></item><item><title>Fierna</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/fierna/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/fierna/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Fierna Daughter of Belial, with whom she co-rules Phlegethos.
Description Appearance Personality Described as fiery and even recklessly passionate.
Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Ignaroz</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/ignaroz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/ignaroz/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Ignaroz Assistant to Carmen (?) who facilitates creation and administration of Tymphal&amp;rsquo;s Contract with the The Menagerie.
Description Appearance First Meeting the Party a female spined devil, with white spines.</description></item><item><title>Keith Stone</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/keith-stone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/keith-stone/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Keith Stone Stone Giant that provides hospitality for the party on the Road of Cinders.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Magrin</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magrin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magrin/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Magrin A duergar who serves served as a chief manager of Tymphal&amp;rsquo;s operations.
Description Appearance Initial Meeting in the Torture Room at Fierna&amp;rsquo;s Tower a now frail and despondent duergar, heavily beaten and lacking teeth After Tymphal&amp;rsquo;s Punishment Magrin&amp;rsquo;s essence is now confined within a green steel shield.</description></item><item><title>Melkor</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/melkor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/melkor/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Melkor Contact that used to work at the tower
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Psithyron</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/psithyron/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/psithyron/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Psithyron An imp which still remains in the service of Horns, back from when Horns was a general of Hell.
Description Appearance Personality Impish.
Biography Key Info Early on in the campaign, Psithyron manifested as a small, devilish figure that Horns had with him when he washed ashore on the beach and Reidoth found him.</description></item><item><title>Quilnorae</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/quilnorae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/quilnorae/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Quilnorae Reportedly an elvish paladin whose soul ended up in a Soul Coin in Fierna&amp;rsquo;s tower.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Aeortis issues a quest for Oneshoe to retrieve the coin with the soul of Quilnorae.</description></item><item><title>Tymphal</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/tymphal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/tymphal/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Tymphal A duke of Phlegethos, Tymphal was a mechanical master smith whose lesser devil legions and hundreds of duergar slaves toiled in a volcano forge to produce weapons and infernal constructs.</description></item><item><title>Veshvor</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/veshvor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/veshvor/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Veshvor A patron of The Brimstone who crossed Magnanimy.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Veshvor won a special necklace from Magnanimy. Magnanimy took offense to Veshvor&amp;rsquo;s behavior and asked Rinn&amp;rsquo;thalas to secure the return of the necklace in exchange for some information.</description></item><item><title>Wrath the Chain Devil</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/wrath-the-chain-devil/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/wrath-the-chain-devil/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Wrath the Chain Devil A powerful chain devil who reportedly may know something about the whereabouts of Ze&amp;rsquo;brak.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Magnanimy claimed that Ze&amp;rsquo;brak may have drawn the ire of Wrath.</description></item><item><title>Zarinor</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zarinor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zarinor/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Zarinor A white dragon, found bound in chains on the 42nd-floor during the Caper at Fierna&amp;rsquo;s Tower.
Description Appearance Large-sized, white dragon.
Personality Abnormally docile and intelligent for a smaller white dragon.</description></item><item><title>2022 01 05</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/05/2022-01-05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/05/2022-01-05/</guid><description>After the relative success last session stealthily clearing out the southeastern perimeter of the tower, the party initially follows a similar tactic: luring guards in small groups into the library to be dispatched quietly. Things go well at first. Then Val suddenly leaves the party to chat up a dragon, and when the group tries to follow, Zed gets the attention of a guardian hellhound, which alerts some of the more powerful devils in the tower.</description></item><item><title>Magnanimy</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magnanimy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magnanimy/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Magnanimy A regular patron of the The Brimstone, who seems to traffic in information.
Description Looks to be a tiefling-ish, higher-class gentleman.
Biography Key Info Magnanimy is fond of gambling.</description></item><item><title>2021 12 22</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/12/22/2021-12-22/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/12/22/2021-12-22/</guid><description>Oneshoe took point leading the party as they explored the first set of rooms along the perimeter of the tower going from Southwest corner counterclockwise towards the East. They find some torture victims and survive the activation of a devious torture chamber themselves. One of the party&amp;rsquo;s targets has been found. No sign of Magrin yet.</description></item><item><title>collecting blood for fun and profit</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/28/collecting-blood-for-fun-and-profit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 23:22:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/28/collecting-blood-for-fun-and-profit/</guid><description>Horns grows a pair of wings, and Cassandra agrees to help the party in exchange for the &lt;em>bag of devouring.&lt;/em> A tortle named Krull escorts the Menagerie from Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower to Arkhan himself. They negotiate a trade of the &lt;em>orb of dragonkind&lt;/em> for a vial of Tiamat&amp;rsquo;s blood and Val backs down from dueling Arkhan. Uldrak&amp;rsquo;s empyrean form is restored, and on the way back to the Demon Zapper the party stops at a conveniently-relocated Wandering Emporium to shelter from an acid storm.</description></item><item><title>Krull</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/krull/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/krull/</guid><description>Description Appearance A male tortle.
Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>of motorcycles and newtonian physics</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/22/of-motorcycles-and-newtonian-physics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 09:19:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/22/of-motorcycles-and-newtonian-physics/</guid><description>The Menagerie approach Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower and, upon seeing it guarded by a dragon, decide to recuperate and gather their strength instead of rushing in. Gimble casts &lt;em>identify&lt;/em> on the &lt;em>orb of dragonkind.&lt;/em> Gray is paid a visit by the Raven Queen who delivers an intercepted letter and a warning against the Feywild. A devilish warband starts a fight, and the party makes a new drow acquaintance.</description></item><item><title>Cassandra Belacourt</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/cassandra-belacourt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/cassandra-belacourt/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Cassandra Belacourt Agent of The Reclamation &amp;ndash; a party which seeks to reclaim artifacts that should not be out in the wild.
Description Appearance A female drow.</description></item><item><title>stack.push(quest)</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/14/stack-push-quest/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 09:19:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/14/stack-push-quest/</guid><description>Red Ruth tells the party that Ralzala can be freed by drinking the blood of a titan, and conveniently also divulges the location of a titan named Uldrak. The Menagerie names their infernal warmachine &amp;ldquo;the Anti-Chrysler&amp;rdquo; and goes to pay Uldrak a visit, but they&amp;rsquo;re diverted yet again by the need to restore his titan form. They set course for Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower, and are attacked by vrocks along the way.</description></item><item><title>Arkhan</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/arkhan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/arkhan/</guid><description>Description A male red chromatic dragonborn.
Appearance Personality Biography A devout follower of Tiamat, he maintains a tower on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Arkhan's Tower</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/arkhans-tower/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/arkhans-tower/</guid><description>Map Key Info An obelisk capped with five large spikes, defended by obsidian ramparts and several patrolling dragons.
Location Avernus, in the Nine Hells of Baator.
Residents Arkhan the Cruel</description></item><item><title>Tiamat</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/tiamat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/tiamat/</guid><description>Description Appearance A gargantuan five-headed dragon, each head being one of the five types of chromatic dragons.
Personality Biography The (evil) Queen of (chromatic) Dragons, Tiamat is imprisoned somewhere on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator.</description></item><item><title>Uldrak</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/uldrak/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/uldrak/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography The empyrean Uldrak quested into the Nine Hells to slay Tiamat and win glory for his deity, Surtur, but he was beaten handily by the dragon queen.</description></item><item><title>friendly fire</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/08/friendly-fire/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/08/friendly-fire/</guid><description>The Menagerie set up camp in Red Ruth&amp;rsquo;s yard to house-sit while she&amp;rsquo;s away. In the middle of resting, they&amp;rsquo;re attacked by banshees and a treant! Gimble learns a little about arcane edge cases, Not-Bailey dies for a moment, Horns becomes a fire elemental, and Finn feeds the treant to a bag.</description></item><item><title>avernian errands</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/31/avernian-errands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/31/avernian-errands/</guid><description>The Menagerie meet Red Ruth and she tells them her price for the information about Ralzala that they want. They Tokyo-drift through the lava geysers of the fire plains and arrive at the Wandering Emporium to book Red Ruth&amp;rsquo;s spa visit. While at the Wandering Emporium, Horns has a beer and the crew do a small amount of shopping before racing back across the fire plains to house-sit for Red Ruth while she takes herself out for a spa day.</description></item><item><title>Fort Knucklebone</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/fort-knucklebone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/fort-knucklebone/</guid><description>Map Key Info A fortified outpost on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator. Ruled by Mad Maggie</description></item><item><title>Mad Maggie</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/mad-maggie/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/mad-maggie/</guid><description>Description A female night hag.
Appearance Personality Biography Head honcho of Fort Knucklebones, a fortified outpost on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Mahadi</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/mahadi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/mahadi/</guid><description>Description A male rakshasa.
Appearance Personality Biography Owner of the Wandering Emporium (commonly found somewhere on the layer Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator), and proprietor of Infernal Rapture.</description></item><item><title>The Wandering Emporium</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/the-wandering-emporium/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/the-wandering-emporium/</guid><description>Key Info “All are welcome here. No fighting! No spellcasting! No exceptions!”
― sign at the entrance of the Wandering Emporium
Owner Mahadi is the master of the Wandering Emporium and proprietor of the Infernal Rapture.</description></item><item><title>Bel</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/bel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/bel/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography Unwilling advisor and second-in-command to Zariel on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>hashtag not all bags</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/25/hashtag-not-all-bags/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/25/hashtag-not-all-bags/</guid><description>Lulu remembers some locations that may help the party find Zariel&amp;rsquo;s ring, and the group travels to a weapon known as the Demon Zapper. They meet Ralzala, a dao who guards the Demon Zapper, and undertake a quest to find Red Ruth in the Bone Brambles for information on Ralzala&amp;rsquo;s behalf. Oneshoe almost gets eaten by a malevolent purse.</description></item><item><title>Ralzala</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/ralzala/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/ralzala/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography A dao who was responsible for guarding the Demon Zapper on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Red Ruth</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/red-ruth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/red-ruth/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography A hag who lives in the Bone Brambles, a region in Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>"zed's folly"</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/10/zeds-folly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/07/10/zeds-folly/</guid><description>The consequences of Horns&amp;rsquo; and Zed&amp;rsquo;s actions result in a confrontation against an opponent capable of dropping Zed. The Menagerie save Lulu from being hollyphantnapped by a hellwasp.</description></item><item><title>Haruman</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/haruman/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/haruman/</guid><description>Description A narzugon that the Menagerie encountered in Avernus, the first layer of the Nine Hells of Baator.
Appearance Personality Biography He had been one of Zariel&amp;rsquo;s generals in the time before her fall, and when her host crashed and broke upon the infernal legions, Haruman took it upon himself to deliver judgement upon those of the host who deserted the cause.</description></item><item><title>Lulu</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/lulu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/lulu/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography A tiny hollyphant that the party met while on Avernus in the Nine Hells of Baator who once was a longtime friend and ally to Zariel before her fall.</description></item><item><title>The Nine Hells of Baator</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/the-nine-hells-of-baator/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/the-nine-hells-of-baator/</guid><description>Map Key Info A lawful evil plane containing nine separate layers of torment:
Avernus Dis Minauros Phlegethos Stygia Malbolge Maladomini Cania Nessus</description></item><item><title>Zariel</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zariel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zariel/</guid><description>Description Appearance Personality Biography The archduchess of Avernus, first layer of the Nine Hells of Baator.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item></channel></rss>