<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>notes on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/</link><description>Recent content in notes on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On Traveling</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/on-traveling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/on-traveling/</guid><description>Neverwinter -&amp;gt; Chult Calculations By Sea Distance from Neverwinter to the southern tip of the Tethyr Peninsula, following the coast as a ship would: ≈ 1600 miles.
On this map it&amp;rsquo;s roughly 16 hexes from the southern tip of the Tethyr Peninsula to Port Nyanzaru as a ship would sail, cutting along the west side of the eastern islands south of the peninsula. Each hex is roughly 25 miles, so 16 * 25 = 400 miles.</description></item><item><title>Paper Crane Letter to Gray</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/grays-paper-crane-letter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/grays-paper-crane-letter/</guid><description>I pray the missive I received was a cruel joke by some nameless charlatan, for I had thought my mourning finished. I pray this letter finds no home, but drifts upon the wind, forever undelivered.
It is not safe for you to contact me like this.
It is not safe for you to be alive.</description></item><item><title>Val's Abyssal Note</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/abyssal-note/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/abyssal-note/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve fought through the haze for what I fear will be the last time. I hope there remain moments enough to draft this warning and to scatter it far enough beyond my reach.
I can no longer remember much of my life before my Queen. In the beginning - when I was still&amp;hellip; Ralain? - I recall fighting against the fungal hallucinations. It was overwhelming, too much information devoid of structure.</description></item><item><title>Tymphal's Contract</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/tymphals-contract/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/tymphals-contract/</guid><description>CONTRACTED WORK AGREEMENT This Contracted Work Agreement (the “Agreement”) is entered into by and between TYMPHAL (the “Client”) and , (the “Mortals”), collectively “the Parties.”
THEREFORE, the Parties agree as follows:
1. Services The Client requests and the Mortals agree to perform the following specific Services (the “Services”):
The Mortals will find Magrin and bring him back to the Client, either alive or within the given Soul Coin. 2. Compensation The Mortals will be compensated as follows:</description></item><item><title>The Calendar of Harptos</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/calendar-of-harptos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 09:20:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/notes/calendar-of-harptos/</guid><description>Information in this article is pulled from Sword Coast Adventurer&amp;rsquo;s Guide, pages 14-15.
There are thirty days (three tendays, or &amp;ldquo;rides&amp;rdquo;) in each month and five annual holidays that fall between months that make up a year of 365 days on the world of Toril. Once every four years, Shieldmeet occurs as a leap day.
Month Name Common Name 1 Hammer Deepwinter Annual Holiday: Midwinter 2 Alturiak The Claw of Winter 3 Ches The Claw of Sunsets 4 Tarsahk The Claw of Storms Annual Holiday: Greengrass 5 Mirtul The Melting 6 Kythorn The Time of Flowers 7 Flamerule Summertide Annual Holiday: Midsummer Quadrennial Holiday: Shieldmeet 8 Eleasis Highsun 9 Elient The Fading Annual Holiday: Highharvestide 10 Marpenoth Leaffall 11 Uktar The Rotting Annual Holiday: The Feast of the Moon 12 Nightal The Drawing Down</description></item></channel></rss>