<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My/DND/Campaigns/Import_campaign/Characters/NPC/Other on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/tags/my/dnd/campaigns/import_campaign/characters/npc/other/</link><description>Recent content in My/DND/Campaigns/Import_campaign/Characters/NPC/Other on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/tags/my/dnd/campaigns/import_campaign/characters/npc/other/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elirion'tar</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/eliriontar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/eliriontar/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Elirion&amp;rsquo;tar Brother to Val and was found working on a ship docked in Neverwinter.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Said he was on way to Chult and said the party could meet him later. Relationships Val Ellie is one of Val&amp;rsquo;s brothers. Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Belial</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/belial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/belial/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Belial Belial is the lord of Phlegethos, who jointly rules the fourth layer together with his daughter Fierna. This unusual partnership was allowed by Asmodeus as an exception to the usual requirement of one ruler per layer.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Fierna Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Fierna</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/fierna/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/fierna/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Fierna Daughter of Belial, with whom she co-rules Phlegethos.
Description Appearance Personality Described as fiery and even recklessly passionate.
Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Magrin</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magrin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magrin/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Magrin A duergar who serves served as a chief manager of Tymphal&amp;rsquo;s operations.
Description Appearance Initial Meeting in the Torture Room at Fierna&amp;rsquo;s Tower a now frail and despondent duergar, heavily beaten and lacking teeth After Tymphal&amp;rsquo;s Punishment Magrin&amp;rsquo;s essence is now confined within a green steel shield.
Magrin&amp;rsquo;s Betrayal is a sentient shield made by an archdevil of Phlegethos, Tymphal, that houses the soul coin of Magrin, his once loyal assistant.</description></item><item><title>Melkor</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/melkor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/melkor/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Melkor Contact that used to work at the tower
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Oberon</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/oberon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/oberon/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Oberon Oberon, Lord of Beasts, consort of Queen Titania, and member of the Seelie Court.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Incensed by the assassination attempt on Queen Titania that left her comatose, Oberon has been leading an unending form of The Wild Hunt. Oberon suspects the parts was involved in the assassination attempt. Relationships Queen Titania As the consort of the queen, Oberon and Titania have a legendarily tempestuous relationship.</description></item><item><title>Queen Titania</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/queen-titania/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/queen-titania/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Queen Titania Archfey and queen of the Summer Court of the Feywild.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info While the party visited the Court of Stars, they witnessed an assassination attempt on Queen Titania which left her gravely injured. The party was imprisoned in oubliettes on suspicion of their involvement in the attack. There are indications that Caerwyn may have been involved in the assassination and/or coverup. From last reports, Queen Titania is still in a comatose state, and this has caused Oberon to rage with an unending Wild Hunt.</description></item><item><title>Quilnorae</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/quilnorae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/quilnorae/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Quilnorae Reportedly an elvish paladin whose soul ended up in a Soul Coin in Fierna&amp;rsquo;s tower.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Aeortis issues a quest for Oneshoe to retrieve the coin with the soul of Quilnorae. Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Tymphal</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/tymphal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/tymphal/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Tymphal A duke of Phlegethos, Tymphal was a mechanical master smith whose lesser devil legions and hundreds of duergar slaves toiled in a volcano forge to produce weapons and infernal constructs.
Description Appearance An immense, imposing figure&amp;ndash;a sort of mixture of golem and fiend. He sports a pair of enormous wings, but his great bulk makes it seem improbably that they could actually carry him aloft.
Personality Absorbed in coordinating his operations, Tymphal seemingly thought the party was beneath his interest and did not deign to speak to them directly.</description></item><item><title>Veshvor</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/veshvor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/veshvor/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Veshvor A patron of The Brimstone who crossed Magnanimy.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Veshvor won a special necklace from Magnanimy. Magnanimy took offense to Veshvor&amp;rsquo;s behavior and asked Rinn&amp;rsquo;thalas to secure the return of the necklace in exchange for some information. In 2021-11-10 Import Campaign Teambuilding through Larceny, Rinn&amp;rsquo;thalas, Gray, and Oneshoe worked together to steal the necklace back from Veshvor. Showed ability to charm others, which he unsuccessfully attempted on Gray.</description></item><item><title>Waybert Spinzig</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/waybert-spinzig/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/waybert-spinzig/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Waybert Spinzig A gnome researcher who arrived in Phandalin along with Zilry to study the incoming Modron March.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Zilry Zilry is a companion who joins in Wayberts&amp;rsquo;s study.
Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Wrath the Chain Devil</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/wrath-the-chain-devil/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/wrath-the-chain-devil/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Wrath the Chain Devil A powerful chain devil who reportedly may know something about the whereabouts of Ze&amp;rsquo;brak.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Magnanimy claimed that Ze&amp;rsquo;brak may have drawn the ire of Wrath. Wrath may be located in the Jangling Hiter. Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Zarinor</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zarinor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zarinor/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Zarinor A white dragon, found bound in chains on the 42nd-floor during the Caper at Fierna&amp;rsquo;s Tower.
Description Appearance Large-sized, white dragon.
Personality Abnormally docile and intelligent for a smaller white dragon.
Biography Zarinor was slain and had her horde stolen by another dragon, Harion.
Key Info Zarinor asks Val to venture to a location in the far north of the Sword Coast to find and slay Harion.</description></item><item><title>Zilry</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zilry/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zilry/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Zilry An elf researcher who arrived in Phandalin along with Waybert to study the incoming Modron March.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Waybert Spinzig Waybert is a companion who joins in Zilry&amp;rsquo;s study.
Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Magnanimy</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magnanimy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magnanimy/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Magnanimy A regular patron of the The Brimstone, who seems to traffic in information.
Description Looks to be a tiefling-ish, higher-class gentleman.
Biography Key Info Magnanimy is fond of gambling. He is less fond of losing to those with poor manners. He offers Rinn&amp;rsquo;thalas information on the whereabouts of Ze&amp;rsquo;brak, in exchange for the return of a certain item taken from him by another patron at The Brimstone.</description></item><item><title>The Tinkerer</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/the-tinkerer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/the-tinkerer/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Harold Peters You know, the Tinkerer.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Originally from the Sword Coast, Harold Peters (you know, the Tinkerer) somehow found himself lost in Shadow Leilon. At some point, his wife died, and he was so overcome with grief that he beseeched the Brownstone Spire for her return. His wish was granted, though in a cruel fashion.
Relationships Key Info Quotations Trivia References</description></item></channel></rss>