<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mortality:alive on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/tags/mortalityalive/</link><description>Recent content in Mortality:alive on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 01:08:56 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/dnd/tags/mortalityalive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brooke</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/brooke/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/brooke/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Brooke Brooke became the proprietor of The Sleeping Giant in Phandalin after The Redbrands were run out of town.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Gray states the Brooke is a secret member of The Wolves.</description></item><item><title>Gundren Rockseeker</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/gundren-rockseeker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/gundren-rockseeker/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Gundren Rockseeker Gundren Rockseeker was one of the three dwarf brothers who rediscovered Wave Echo Cave.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Late Brothers brother to Tharden Rockseeker older brother to Nundro Rockseeker Val Gundren and Val become fast friends and drinking buddies.</description></item><item><title>Waybert Spinzig</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/waybert-spinzig/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/waybert-spinzig/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Waybert Spinzig A gnome researcher who arrived in Phandalin along with Zilry to study the incoming Modron March.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Zilry Zilry is a companion who joins in Wayberts&amp;rsquo;s study.</description></item><item><title>Cassandra Belacourt</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/cassandra-belacourt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/cassandra-belacourt/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Cassandra Belacourt Agent of The Reclamation &amp;ndash; a party which seeks to reclaim artifacts that should not be out in the wild.
Description Appearance A female drow.</description></item><item><title>Finn</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/finn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/finn/</guid><description> Halfling Barbarian (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
the “conjurer” #LowIntLifeLessons friend to Not-Bailey don’t ask about Bailey Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Gimble the Diviner</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble-the-diviner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble-the-diviner/</guid><description>Gimble the Diviner gnome wizard (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
“the diviner” moral compass always flustered family matters Description Appearance Gimble is a rock gnome standing just over three feet tall. He has blue eyes and chestnut hair which tends to be a frazzled mess, spiking upwards.</description></item><item><title>Haeltin Var Astora</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/haeltin-var-astora/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/haeltin-var-astora/</guid><description>Haeltin Var Astora half-drow blood hunter (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
goes by &amp;ldquo;Gray&amp;rdquo; formerly Haeltin Var Astora formerly a paladin formerly deceased anime werewolf motorcycle boi Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Alter egos Jared Gray took on the persona of &amp;ldquo;Jared&amp;rdquo; several times in the Sword Coast.</description></item><item><title>Horns</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/horns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/horns/</guid><description>Horns tiefling druid (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
knows trees&amp;rsquo; weak points formerly a general in the Blood War probably not evil - like, probably new and improved, now with wings! Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Mirna Dendrar</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/mirna-dendrar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/mirna-dendrar/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Mirna Dendrar Description Human commoner from Phandalin Biography When she was a young girl, she and her family fled from the town of Thundertree after undead overran the place.</description></item><item><title>Oneshoe</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/oneshoe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/oneshoe/</guid><description>Oneshoe Gnome Rogue/Warlock (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
professional detective business owner don’t ask about the other shoe goddammit Harold Description Appearance Oneshoe is a rock gnome. Her brown hair is cut with asymmetrical bangs, which helps to hide some burn scars on the left side of her face.</description></item><item><title>Reidoth</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/reidoth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/reidoth/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Reidoth Description Reidoth is a gaunt, white-bearded human who doesn&amp;rsquo;t use two words when one word will do. Though he receives very few visitors, he is reasonably hospitable.</description></item><item><title>Rinn'thalas Liadon</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/rinnthalas-liadon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/rinnthalas-liadon/</guid><description>Rinn&amp;rsquo;thalas Liadon Wood Elf Horizon Walker Ranger DND Beyond
Description Appearance Personality Biography Background With Menagerie in Baator Relationships Ze&amp;rsquo;brak Gorstag Character Info Quests Deliver a letter to the party (a favor for Gorstag orchestrated by Gimble) Find his lost friend, Ze&amp;rsquo;brak Notable Items Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Sildar Hallwinter</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/sildar-hallwinter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/sildar-hallwinter/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Sildar Hallwinter Human soldier and member of the Lords&amp;rsquo; Alliance who accompanies Gundren Rockseeker on travel from Neverwinter to Phandalin.
Description Appearance Personality Seemed sincere in his desire to help the townsfolk of Phandalin.</description></item><item><title>Sister Garaele</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/sister-garaele/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/sister-garaele/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Sister Garaele Description Elf cleric of Tymora who tends the Luck Shrine in town.
Biography Key Info member of The Harpers sent party on a quest to get information from a banshee named Agatha about the location of Bowgentle&amp;rsquo;s spellbook Relationships Gimble Taught Gimble the ritual for Gentle Repose Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>The Tinkerer</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/the-tinkerer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/the-tinkerer/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Harold Peters You know, the Tinkerer.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Originally from the Sword Coast, Harold Peters (you know, the Tinkerer) somehow found himself lost in Shadow Leilon.</description></item><item><title>Val</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/val/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/val/</guid><description>Val wood elf druid (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
never surprised flexible morality a real dwarf’s elf some kind of royalty Description Appearance Personality Biography Born as Nadyantal&amp;rsquo;laval Has a brother, Elirion&amp;rsquo;tar. Apparently, Val has other siblings, including an eldest brother.</description></item><item><title>Zed</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/zed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/characters/zed/</guid><description>Zed half-orc paladin (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
kindle the yoga powerful thighs “Bullwinkle take the wheel” the puns start coming and they never stop coming and they never stop coming and they never stop coming Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item></channel></rss>