<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cassandra Belacourt on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/cassandra-belacourt/</link><description>Recent content in Cassandra Belacourt on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 01:08:56 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/cassandra-belacourt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flying into the Night</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/11/08/flying-into-the-night/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/11/08/flying-into-the-night/</guid><description>With portents that Nyx may be in danger, Gimble plans to leave Candlekeep. Before they leave, Val receives an intriguing quest from the Head Reader, and Cassandra Belacourt gives the party a faster means to travel towards Nyx&amp;rsquo;s likely location. The party briefly pass through Silverymoon before attempting to track down a hidden Nxy before they are too late.</description></item><item><title>Research Obstructing Research</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/02/research-obstructing-research/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/02/research-obstructing-research/</guid><description>Gimble&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em>contact other plane&lt;/em> goes a little off the rails, and he has a conversation with Gruumsh. The group try to come up with a new plan for dealing with Nyx&amp;rsquo;s pursuers, since their charade in Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate failed to pull them off of Nyx&amp;rsquo;s trail. Val tours the Court of Air looking for any possible way to get past the Emerald Door. Cassandra visits, and the first round of requested knowledge is delievered.</description></item><item><title>Arrival in Candlekeep</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/06/21/arrival-in-candlekeep/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/06/21/arrival-in-candlekeep/</guid><description>The party gains entry into Candlekeep and its outer Court of Air, but they are barred investigating the inner library themselves, despite Gimble&amp;rsquo;s insistence. Instead, they fill out numerous research requests and seek lodging to rest and prepare for what comes next.</description></item><item><title>A Study in Synthwave</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</guid><description>Psithyron displays his latest masterpiece. Gray opens up more about his family. A desperate message from Finn is foreseen, and a gnome returns. The party considers their options, and a bold, but likely foolish plan is made.</description></item><item><title>catch-22 items</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/09/05/catch-22-items/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 23:22:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/09/05/catch-22-items/</guid><description>The Menagerie make several purchases from &lt;em>Grundle &amp;amp; Chode&amp;rsquo;s Arcane Boutique,&lt;/em> including a retainer for druids who like talking while wild-shaped. Gimble reaches a breaking point and leaves the party.</description></item><item><title>collecting blood for fun and profit</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/28/collecting-blood-for-fun-and-profit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 23:22:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/28/collecting-blood-for-fun-and-profit/</guid><description>Horns grows a pair of wings, and Cassandra agrees to help the party in exchange for the &lt;em>bag of devouring.&lt;/em> A tortle named Krull escorts the Menagerie from Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower to Arkhan himself. They negotiate a trade of the &lt;em>orb of dragonkind&lt;/em> for a vial of Tiamat&amp;rsquo;s blood and Val backs down from dueling Arkhan. Uldrak&amp;rsquo;s empyrean form is restored, and on the way back to the Demon Zapper the party stops at a conveniently-relocated Wandering Emporium to shelter from an acid storm.</description></item><item><title>of motorcycles and newtonian physics</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/22/of-motorcycles-and-newtonian-physics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 09:19:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/08/22/of-motorcycles-and-newtonian-physics/</guid><description>The Menagerie approach Arkhan&amp;rsquo;s tower and, upon seeing it guarded by a dragon, decide to recuperate and gather their strength instead of rushing in. Gimble casts &lt;em>identify&lt;/em> on the &lt;em>orb of dragonkind.&lt;/em> Gray is paid a visit by the Raven Queen who delivers an intercepted letter and a warning against the Feywild. A devilish warband starts a fight, and the party makes a new drow acquaintance.</description></item><item><title>Cassandra Belacourt</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/cassandra-belacourt/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/cassandra-belacourt/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Cassandra Belacourt Agent of The Reclamation &amp;ndash; a party which seeks to reclaim artifacts that should not be out in the wild.
Description Appearance A female drow.</description></item></channel></rss>