<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>characters on tlake.io</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/</link><description>Recent content in characters on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><atom:link href="http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dilemma at the Aboleth's Lair</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble/dilemma-at-the-aboleths-lair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble/dilemma-at-the-aboleths-lair/</guid><description>Gimble the Diviner
Dilemma at the Aboleth&amp;rsquo;s Lair In Shadow Leilon, Gimble was finally able to locate his missing sister and aunt in the depths of the aboleth&amp;rsquo;s lair in 2019-08-09 Import Campaign.</description></item><item><title>Finn</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/finn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/finn/</guid><description> Halfling Barbarian (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
the “conjurer” #LowIntLifeLessons friend to Not-Bailey don’t ask about Bailey Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Gimble Became Lawful Evil in Avernus</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble/gimble-became-lawful-evil-in-avernus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble/gimble-became-lawful-evil-in-avernus/</guid><description>Gimble the Diviner
Gimble Became Lawful Evil in Avernus After being dragged to Hell (literally) by the party, Gimble eventually succumbed to the pernicious nature of Avernus and shifted to a lawful evil outlook.</description></item><item><title>Gimble prepares special defensive magic for Finn</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble/gimble-prepares-special-defensive-magic-for-finn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble/gimble-prepares-special-defensive-magic-for-finn/</guid><description>Gimble the Diviner
Gimble prepares special defensive magic for Finn When Gimble Became Lawful Evil in Avernus, he new he had to leave the Hells. However, his lingering friendship with Finn compelled him to first make some special castings into his Ioun stone and give it to Finn, hoping it would help keep her safe.</description></item><item><title>Gimble the Diviner</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble-the-diviner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble-the-diviner/</guid><description>Gimble the Diviner gnome wizard (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
“the diviner” moral compass always flustered family matters Description Appearance Gimble is a rock gnome standing just over three feet tall. He has blue eyes and chestnut hair which tends to be a frazzled mess, spiking upwards.</description></item><item><title>Gimble the Diviner Backstory</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble/gimble-the-diviner-backstory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble/gimble-the-diviner-backstory/</guid><description>Gimble the Diviner
Gimble the Diviner Backstory Formatted Gimble the Diviner Backstory &amp;ndash; Formatted
Text Version Gimble seeks to unravel the mystery of a strange, blank book and its connection to his lost sister.</description></item><item><title>Gorstag</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gorstag/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gorstag/</guid><description>Gorstag human fighter (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
trans-dimensional gambling baron rolls with anything occasional corrective community service portal technology: unknown Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Grale</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/grale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/grale/</guid><description>Grale half-orc monk/ranger (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
like, three Narutos, and also a Goku shadow run (but not like the rpg) stuns for days biggus stickus Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Haeltin Var Astora</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/haeltin-var-astora/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/haeltin-var-astora/</guid><description>Haeltin Var Astora half-drow blood hunter (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
goes by &amp;ldquo;Gray&amp;rdquo; formerly Haeltin Var Astora formerly a paladin formerly deceased anime werewolf motorcycle boi Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Alter egos Jared Gray took on the persona of &amp;ldquo;Jared&amp;rdquo; several times in the Sword Coast.</description></item><item><title>Horns</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/horns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/horns/</guid><description>Horns tiefling druid (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
knows trees&amp;rsquo; weak points formerly a general in the Blood War probably not evil - like, probably new and improved, now with wings! Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Ivor Borst</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/ivor-borst/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/ivor-borst/</guid><description>Ivor Borst human barbarian
no door is safe Loviatar - wait, WHAT Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>JSON</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/json/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/json/</guid><description>JSON wood elf bard
out on tour the greatest insult to black puddings Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Kithri Tealeaf</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/kithri-tealeaf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/kithri-tealeaf/</guid><description>Kithri Tealeaf halfling rogue
surprisingly nice, for a rogue Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Mindartis</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/mindartis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/mindartis/</guid><description>Mindartis wood elf rogue
master looter somewhere else Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Oneshoe</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/oneshoe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/oneshoe/</guid><description>Oneshoe Gnome Rogue/Warlock (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
professional detective business owner don’t ask about the other shoe goddammit Harold Description Appearance Oneshoe is a rock gnome. Her brown hair is cut with asymmetrical bangs, which helps to hide some burn scars on the left side of her face.</description></item><item><title>Orsik Stoneskin</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/orsik-stoneskin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/orsik-stoneskin/</guid><description>Orsik Stoneskin dwarf monk
is he still at Old Owl Well? Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Rinn'thalas Liadon</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/rinnthalas-liadon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/rinnthalas-liadon/</guid><description>Rinn&amp;rsquo;thalas Liadon Wood Elf Horizon Walker Ranger DND Beyond
Description Appearance Personality Biography Background With Menagerie in Baator Relationships Ze&amp;rsquo;brak Gorstag Character Info Quests Deliver a letter to the party (a favor for Gorstag orchestrated by Gimble) Find his lost friend, Ze&amp;rsquo;brak Notable Items Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>That time Val tried to murder Gimble</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble/that-time-val-tried-to-murder-gimble/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/gimble/that-time-val-tried-to-murder-gimble/</guid><description>Gimble the Diviner
That time Val tried to murder Gimble When the party became 5th level, Gimble had a premonition that he would very soon need the ability to fly. Obsessed with this, he absentmindedly plucked a feather from Val&amp;rsquo;s new Giant Owl form for a spell component to aid in his furious study.</description></item><item><title>Val</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/val/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/val/</guid><description>Val wood elf druid (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
never surprised flexible morality a real dwarf’s elf some kind of royalty Description Appearance Personality Biography Born as Nadyantal&amp;rsquo;laval Has a brother, Elirion&amp;rsquo;tar. Apparently, Val has other siblings, including an eldest brother.</description></item><item><title>Zane a Presque Du'Cal</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/zane-a-presque-ducal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/zane-a-presque-ducal/</guid><description>Zane a Presque Du’Cal half-elf bard
deceased savaged by a Gray wolf misguider of innocents Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item><item><title>Zed</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/zed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/characters/zed/</guid><description>Zed half-orc paladin (D&amp;amp;D Beyond)
kindle the yoga powerful thighs “Bullwinkle take the wheel” the puns start coming and they never stop coming and they never stop coming and they never stop coming Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Character Information Quotations Trivia References</description></item></channel></rss>