<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Benedora Stoneforge on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/benedora-stoneforge/</link><description>Recent content in Benedora Stoneforge on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 17:26:22 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/benedora-stoneforge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flying into the Night</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/11/08/flying-into-the-night/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/11/08/flying-into-the-night/</guid><description>With portents that Nyx may be in danger, Gimble plans to leave Candlekeep. Before they leave, Val receives an intriguing quest from the Head Reader, and Cassandra Belacourt gives the party a faster means to travel towards Nyx&amp;rsquo;s likely location. The party briefly pass through Silverymoon before attempting to track down a hidden Nxy before they are too late.</description></item><item><title>A Remnant of Faith</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/10/25/a-remnant-of-faith/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/10/25/a-remnant-of-faith/</guid><description>Returned from their literary adventure, the party concludes their current research within the inner library, Val considers the risks of possession, and Gimble gains insight but loses something in the process.</description></item><item><title>The Walk Without Shame</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/30/the-walk-without-shame/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/30/the-walk-without-shame/</guid><description>The party continues processing the results of their research requests, an unsteady Gimble has some troubling revelations at the Temple of Oghma, and Oneshoe enthusiastically takes one for the team. Just as the party considers leaving to find Nyx, they are granted access to The Emerald Door and the interior of Candlekeep.</description></item><item><title>Benedora Stoneforge</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/benedora-stoneforge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/benedora-stoneforge/</guid><description>Description Gold dwarf
Appearance Personality Biography A Keeper of the Emerald Door at Candlekeep.
Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Research Obstructing Research</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/02/research-obstructing-research/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/02/research-obstructing-research/</guid><description>Gimble&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em>contact other plane&lt;/em> goes a little off the rails, and he has a conversation with Gruumsh. The group try to come up with a new plan for dealing with Nyx&amp;rsquo;s pursuers, since their charade in Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate failed to pull them off of Nyx&amp;rsquo;s trail. Val tours the Court of Air looking for any possible way to get past the Emerald Door. Cassandra visits, and the first round of requested knowledge is delievered.</description></item><item><title>Arrival in Candlekeep</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/06/21/arrival-in-candlekeep/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/06/21/arrival-in-candlekeep/</guid><description>The party gains entry into Candlekeep and its outer Court of Air, but they are barred investigating the inner library themselves, despite Gimble&amp;rsquo;s insistence. Instead, they fill out numerous research requests and seek lodging to rest and prepare for what comes next.</description></item></channel></rss>