<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rivermoot on tlake.io</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/locations/rivermoot/</link><description>Recent content in Rivermoot on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 20:14:46 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/locations/rivermoot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Scattered Away</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-01-24/scattered-away/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-01-24/scattered-away/</guid><description>Timber proves to be a powerful foe, and a panicked Nyx sets up a desperate escape. Zed hangs back long enough to flirt with Mountain, and Bullwinkle heroically buys the party some time.</description></item><item><title>Timber Strikes</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-01-10/timber-strikes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-01-10/timber-strikes/</guid><description>Nyx has been found, and the party tries to convince her to fight back against her pursuers. Alone, Gray observes a familiar figure closing in on its prey. Nyx panics and pleads for escape, and Timber strikes. And he is not alone.</description></item><item><title>Flying into the Night</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/11/08/flying-into-the-night/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/11/08/flying-into-the-night/</guid><description>With portents that Nyx may be in danger, Gimble plans to leave Candlekeep. Before they leave, Val receives an intriguing quest from the Head Reader, and Cassandra Belacourt gives the party a faster means to travel towards Nyx&amp;rsquo;s likely location. The party briefly pass through Silverymoon before attempting to track down a hidden Nxy before they are too late.</description></item><item><title>The Walk Without Shame</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/30/the-walk-without-shame/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/30/the-walk-without-shame/</guid><description>The party continues processing the results of their research requests, an unsteady Gimble has some troubling revelations at the Temple of Oghma, and Oneshoe enthusiastically takes one for the team. Just as the party considers leaving to find Nyx, they are granted access to The Emerald Door and the interior of Candlekeep.</description></item></channel></rss>