<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Baator on tlake.io</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/locations/baator/</link><description>Recent content in Baator on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/locations/baator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Baator</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/baator/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/baator/</guid><description>Map Key Info</description></item><item><title>Graz'zt</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/grazzt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 17:09:11 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/grazzt/</guid><description/></item><item><title>2022 03 30</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-03-30/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-03-30/</guid><description>Summary The party&amp;rsquo;s escape from the tower stalls with the realization that they are unable to teleport all of their summoned creatures to safety. Knowing Fierna could locate them any moment, some hard decisions are made at the expense of Zed&amp;rsquo;s minotaur friends, and the Menagerie finally teleports away.</description></item><item><title>2022 03 16</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-03-16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-03-16/</guid><description>Summary Having dispatched the remaining guards in the corridor, the party resumes its search for Magrin. They find a room with six pillars, adorned with piles of teeth&amp;ndash;apparently some ghastly connection to Gelfondi&amp;rsquo;s machine room found earlier.</description></item><item><title>2022 02 16</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-02-16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-02-16/</guid><description>Summary Alone and defiant, Finn squares up against the incoming bone devil and its guard. She is swiftly restrained by a chain devil, and Finn summons her signature flumphs in retribution, but this does not stop the bone devil from savagely attacking Finn with its claws and hideous stinger.</description></item><item><title>2022 02 02</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-02-02/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-02-02/</guid><description>Summary The party carefully creeps along the southern corridor towards the west, hoping to avoid further detection. At the sight of a bone devil ahead, Zed and his minotaurs instead choose to (somehow) squeeze into a small alcove towards the center of the tower, where they uncover two hidden imps keeping watch.</description></item><item><title>Gelfondi</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/gelfondi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/gelfondi/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Gelfondi The devil in charge of the operations on the 42nd floor of Fierna&amp;rsquo;s tower.
Description Appearance Gelfondi is a horned devil, slightly shorter than usual. He was wearing some type or robes when the party surprised him in 2022-02-02 Import Campaign.</description></item><item><title>2022 01 19</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-01-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-01-19/</guid><description>Summary The party desperately tries to dispatch the the two horned devils and subordinate in the main corridor before the devils can alert the guard barracks and the rest of the tower.</description></item><item><title>Aeortis</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/aeortis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/aeortis/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Aeortis An apparent young girl who designed much Fierna&amp;rsquo;s tower.
Description Appearance a (supposed) young girl, accompanied by three hellhounds Personality Biography Relationships Oneshoe In payment for giving information to the party, Aeortis required the party to perform a service for her and retrieve a particular soul coin from Fierna&amp;rsquo;s tower.</description></item><item><title>Belial</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/belial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/belial/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Belial Belial is the lord of Phlegethos, who jointly rules the fourth layer together with his daughter Fierna. This unusual partnership was allowed by Asmodeus as an exception to the usual requirement of one ruler per layer.</description></item><item><title>Carmen</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/carmen/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/carmen/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Carmen Known as one of the most powerful and effective lawyers in Phlegethos.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Due to her extraordinary reputation, Carmen commands exceedingly high fees for her services.</description></item><item><title>Cassandra Belacourt</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/cassandra-belacourt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/cassandra-belacourt/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Cassandra Belacourt Agent of The Reclamation &amp;ndash; a party which seeks to reclaim artifacts that should not be out in the wild.
Description Appearance A female drow.</description></item><item><title>Fierna</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/fierna/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/fierna/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Fierna Daughter of Belial, with whom she co-rules Phlegethos.
Description Appearance Personality Described as fiery and even recklessly passionate.
Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Ignaroz</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/ignaroz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/ignaroz/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Ignaroz Assistant to Carmen (?) who facilitates creation and administration of Tymphal&amp;rsquo;s Contract with the The Menagerie.
Description Appearance First Meeting the Party a female spined devil, with white spines.</description></item><item><title>Keith Stone</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/keith-stone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/keith-stone/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Keith Stone Stone Giant that provides hospitality for the party on the Road of Cinders.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Magrin</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magrin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magrin/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Magrin A duergar who serves served as a chief manager of Tymphal&amp;rsquo;s operations.
Description Appearance Initial Meeting in the Torture Room at Fierna&amp;rsquo;s Tower a now frail and despondent duergar, heavily beaten and lacking teeth After Tymphal&amp;rsquo;s Punishment Magrin&amp;rsquo;s essence is now confined within a green steel shield.</description></item><item><title>Melkor</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/melkor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/melkor/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Melkor Contact that used to work at the tower
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Psithyron</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/psithyron/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/psithyron/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Psithyron An imp which still remains in the service of Horns, back from when Horns was a general of Hell.
Description Appearance Personality Impish.
Biography Key Info Early on in the campaign, Psithyron manifested as a small, devilish figure that Horns had with him when he washed ashore on the beach and Reidoth found him.</description></item><item><title>Quilnorae</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/quilnorae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/quilnorae/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Quilnorae Reportedly an elvish paladin whose soul ended up in a Soul Coin in Fierna&amp;rsquo;s tower.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Aeortis issues a quest for Oneshoe to retrieve the coin with the soul of Quilnorae.</description></item><item><title>Tymphal</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/tymphal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/tymphal/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Tymphal A duke of Phlegethos, Tymphal was a mechanical master smith whose lesser devil legions and hundreds of duergar slaves toiled in a volcano forge to produce weapons and infernal constructs.</description></item><item><title>Veshvor</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/veshvor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/veshvor/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Veshvor A patron of The Brimstone who crossed Magnanimy.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Veshvor won a special necklace from Magnanimy. Magnanimy took offense to Veshvor&amp;rsquo;s behavior and asked Rinn&amp;rsquo;thalas to secure the return of the necklace in exchange for some information.</description></item><item><title>Wrath the Chain Devil</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/wrath-the-chain-devil/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/wrath-the-chain-devil/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Wrath the Chain Devil A powerful chain devil who reportedly may know something about the whereabouts of Ze&amp;rsquo;brak.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Magnanimy claimed that Ze&amp;rsquo;brak may have drawn the ire of Wrath.</description></item><item><title>Zarinor</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zarinor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zarinor/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Zarinor A white dragon, found bound in chains on the 42nd-floor during the Caper at Fierna&amp;rsquo;s Tower.
Description Appearance Large-sized, white dragon.
Personality Abnormally docile and intelligent for a smaller white dragon.</description></item><item><title>2022 01 05</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-01-05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022-01-05/</guid><description>Summary After the relative success last session stealthily clearing out the southeastern perimeter of the tower, the party initially follows a similar tactic: luring guards in small groups into the library to be dispatched quietly.</description></item><item><title>Magnanimy</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magnanimy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magnanimy/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Magnanimy A regular patron of the The Brimstone, who seems to traffic in information.
Description Looks to be a tiefling-ish, higher-class gentleman.
Biography Key Info Magnanimy is fond of gambling.</description></item><item><title>2021 12 22</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021-12-22/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021-12-22/</guid><description>Summary Oneshoe took point leading the party as they explored the first set of rooms along the perimeter of the tower going from Southwest corner counterclockwise towards the East. They find some torture victims and survive the activation of a devious torture chamber themselves.</description></item></channel></rss>