<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My/DND/Campaigns/Import_campaign/Sessions on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/tags/my/dnd/campaigns/import_campaign/sessions/</link><description>Recent content in My/DND/Campaigns/Import_campaign/Sessions on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 21:25:09 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/tags/my/dnd/campaigns/import_campaign/sessions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2022 03 16</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/03/16/2022-03-16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/03/16/2022-03-16/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary Having dispatched the remaining guards in the corridor, the party resumes its search for Magrin. They find a room with six pillars, adorned with piles of teeth&amp;ndash;apparently some ghastly connection to Gelfondi&amp;rsquo;s machine room found earlier.</description></item><item><title>2022 02 16</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/16/2022-02-16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/16/2022-02-16/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary Alone and defiant, Finn squares up against the incoming bone devil and its guard. She is swiftly restrained by a chain devil, and Finn summons her signature flumphs in retribution, but this does not stop the bone devil from savagely attacking Finn with its claws and hideous stinger.</description></item><item><title>2022 02 02</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/02/2022-02-02/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/02/2022-02-02/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary The party carefully creeps along the southern corridor towards the west, hoping to avoid further detection. At the sight of a bone devil ahead, Zed and his minotaurs instead choose to (somehow) squeeze into a small alcove towards the center of the tower, where they uncover two hidden imps keeping watch.</description></item><item><title>2022 01 19</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/19/2022-01-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/19/2022-01-19/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary The party desperately tries to dispatch the the two horned devils and subordinate in the main corridor before the devils can alert the guard barracks and the rest of the tower.</description></item><item><title>2022 01 05</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/05/2022-01-05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/05/2022-01-05/</guid><description>After the relative success last session stealthily clearing out the southeastern perimeter of the tower, the party initially follows a similar tactic: luring guards in small groups into the library to be dispatched quietly. Things go well at first. Then Val suddenly leaves the party to chat up a dragon, and when the group tries to follow, Zed gets the attention of a guardian hellhound, which alerts some of the more powerful devils in the tower.</description></item><item><title>2021 12 22</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/12/22/2021-12-22/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/12/22/2021-12-22/</guid><description>Oneshoe took point leading the party as they explored the first set of rooms along the perimeter of the tower going from Southwest corner counterclockwise towards the East. They find some torture victims and survive the activation of a devious torture chamber themselves. One of the party&amp;rsquo;s targets has been found. No sign of Magrin yet.</description></item><item><title>2021 12 08</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/12/08/2021-12-08/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/12/08/2021-12-08/</guid><description>Another day at court for Horns&amp;rsquo; trial. This time, the prosecution calls Val to the stand. This does not go well for Horns. Later, the party learns that Horns has been secretly hoarding a large stash of soul coins &lt;em>since Avernus&lt;/em>. In the midst of intraparty conflict and high tempers, the party attempts to finalize the plan for the Caper at Fierna&amp;rsquo;s Tower, but they ultimately opt to cut that short and do it live. Teleporting to one of the locations given by Aeortis, the party begins their mission on the 42nd floor.</description></item><item><title>2021 11 10</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/11/10/2021-11-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/11/10/2021-11-10/</guid><description>Rinn&amp;rsquo;thalas learns about cake. Ignaroz meets the party to discuss the upcoming Caper at Fierna&amp;rsquo;s Tower. Rinn leads a few members of the party in some late-night teambuilding through larceny. The party continues their group therapy session during the next day of court proceedings.</description></item><item><title>2021 10 27</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/10/27/2021-10-27/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 23:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/10/27/2021-10-27/</guid><description>After spending some time with the stone giant Keith Stone, the party continues gathering intel for their Caper at Fierna&amp;rsquo;s Tower. They speak with Melkor and later Aeortis, who gives them detailed information about the tower&amp;rsquo;s construction in exchange for a new contract to retrieve something extra from the tower. A letter is delivered to the party by a strange messenger.</description></item><item><title>Ocean's Oneshoe</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/08/04/oceans-oneshoe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 23:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/08/04/oceans-oneshoe/</guid><description>Zed receives news of the Feywild from an old friend before he is later served up as part of a &amp;ldquo;cake&amp;rdquo; buffet delivery to Carmen. The party is approached with an offer of work to pay off Carmen&amp;rsquo;s hefty fee to defend Horns, but it requires making another deal with a devil.</description></item></channel></rss>