<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Queen Titania on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/queen-titania/</link><description>Recent content in Queen Titania on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 01:08:56 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/queen-titania/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Frozen</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-02-07/frozen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-02-07/frozen/</guid><description>The party finds itself back in the Feywild, much changed. Winter reigns. Nyx remains unresponsive. A frigid night brings visions. Gray recounts the danger of the Wild Hunt. Hoping for options, the group heads towards a fey crossing and reaches out to friends for answers.</description></item><item><title>The Walk Without Shame</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/30/the-walk-without-shame/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/30/the-walk-without-shame/</guid><description>The party continues processing the results of their research requests, an unsteady Gimble has some troubling revelations at the Temple of Oghma, and Oneshoe enthusiastically takes one for the team. Just as the party considers leaving to find Nyx, they are granted access to The Emerald Door and the interior of Candlekeep.</description></item><item><title>A Study in Synthwave</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</guid><description>Psithyron displays his latest masterpiece. Gray opens up more about his family. A desperate message from Finn is foreseen, and a gnome returns. The party considers their options, and a bold, but likely foolish plan is made.</description></item><item><title>Queen Titania</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/queen-titania/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/queen-titania/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Queen Titania Archfey and queen of the Summer Court of the Feywild.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info While the party visited the Court of Stars, they witnessed an assassination attempt on Queen Titania which left her gravely injured.</description></item></channel></rss>