<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gundren Rockseeker on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/gundren-rockseeker/</link><description>Recent content in Gundren Rockseeker on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 21:25:09 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/gundren-rockseeker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Study in Synthwave</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</guid><description>Psithyron displays his latest masterpiece. Gray opens up more about his family. A desperate message from Finn is foreseen, and a gnome returns. The party considers their options, and a bold, but likely foolish plan is made.</description></item><item><title>Mea Culpa</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/10/mea-culpa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/10/mea-culpa/</guid><description>The dust has barely settled from the battle with The Revenant, yet the party quickly goes their separate ways. Val takes a weary Gundren out for drinks; Oneshoe tails Finn as she is pulled into a suspicious conversation with Brooke; Horns assesses the damage to his room; and Gray has a vision in the basement. The party finally comes together again the next afternoon, and Gray admits to the group: this has all been his fault, and he needs to leave. A great amount of discord follows. Help is sought from absent allies with unclear results. The party fights about direction but fails to reach any consensus.</description></item><item><title>Vengeance Denied</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/04/26/vengeance-denied/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/04/26/vengeance-denied/</guid><description>Things look dire for most of the party. Then a certain half-orc shows up with some friends, and Horns removes the dragon from play. The tide turns.</description></item><item><title>Burying His Mum's Hatchet</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/04/12/burying-his-mums-hatchet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/04/12/burying-his-mums-hatchet/</guid><description>The revenant has finally located Val, but she stays maddeningly just out of his reach. The burning rage must find a new outlet: her friends.</description></item><item><title>A Terrible Anniversary</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/03/15/a-terrible-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/03/15/a-terrible-anniversary/</guid><description>At long last, Val&amp;rsquo;s relentless pursuer has found her. This time, the revenant brings an undead horde to exact his vengeance, or to destroy anything that would get in his way doing so.</description></item><item><title>Gundren Rockseeker</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/gundren-rockseeker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/gundren-rockseeker/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Gundren Rockseeker Gundren Rockseeker was one of the three dwarf brothers who rediscovered Wave Echo Cave.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Relationships Late Brothers brother to Tharden Rockseeker older brother to Nundro Rockseeker Val Gundren and Val become fast friends and drinking buddies.</description></item></channel></rss>