<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brooke on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/brooke/</link><description>Recent content in Brooke on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 01:08:56 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/brooke/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Study in Synthwave</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</guid><description>Psithyron displays his latest masterpiece. Gray opens up more about his family. A desperate message from Finn is foreseen, and a gnome returns. The party considers their options, and a bold, but likely foolish plan is made.</description></item><item><title>Brooke</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/brooke/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/brooke/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Brooke Brooke became the proprietor of The Sleeping Giant in Phandalin after The Redbrands were run out of town.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Gray states the Brooke is a secret member of The Wolves.</description></item><item><title>Mea Culpa</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/10/mea-culpa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/10/mea-culpa/</guid><description>The dust has barely settled from the battle with The Revenant, yet the party quickly goes their separate ways. Val takes a weary Gundren out for drinks; Oneshoe tails Finn as she is pulled into a suspicious conversation with Brooke; Horns assesses the damage to his room; and Gray has a vision in the basement. The party finally comes together again the next afternoon, and Gray admits to the group: this has all been his fault, and he needs to leave. A great amount of discord follows. Help is sought from absent allies with unclear results. The party fights about direction but fails to reach any consensus.</description></item></channel></rss>