<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fierna's Tower on tlake.io</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/locations/fiernas-tower/</link><description>Recent content in Fierna's Tower on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 21:25:09 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tlake.io/dnd/ref/locations/fiernas-tower/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fierna's Tower</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/fiernas-tower/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/locations/fiernas-tower/</guid><description>Map Key Info</description></item><item><title>2022 03 30</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/03/30/2022-03-30/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/03/30/2022-03-30/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary The party&amp;rsquo;s escape from the tower stalls with the realization that they are unable to teleport all of their summoned creatures to safety. Knowing Fierna could locate them any moment, some hard decisions are made at the expense of Zed&amp;rsquo;s minotaur friends, and the Menagerie finally teleports away.</description></item><item><title>2022 03 16</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/03/16/2022-03-16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/03/16/2022-03-16/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary Having dispatched the remaining guards in the corridor, the party resumes its search for Magrin. They find a room with six pillars, adorned with piles of teeth&amp;ndash;apparently some ghastly connection to Gelfondi&amp;rsquo;s machine room found earlier.</description></item><item><title>2022 02 16</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/16/2022-02-16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/16/2022-02-16/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary Alone and defiant, Finn squares up against the incoming bone devil and its guard. She is swiftly restrained by a chain devil, and Finn summons her signature flumphs in retribution, but this does not stop the bone devil from savagely attacking Finn with its claws and hideous stinger.</description></item><item><title>2022 02 02</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/02/2022-02-02/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/02/02/2022-02-02/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary The party carefully creeps along the southern corridor towards the west, hoping to avoid further detection. At the sight of a bone devil ahead, Zed and his minotaurs instead choose to (somehow) squeeze into a small alcove towards the center of the tower, where they uncover two hidden imps keeping watch.</description></item><item><title>Gelfondi</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/gelfondi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/gelfondi/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Gelfondi The devil in charge of the operations on the 42nd floor of Fierna&amp;rsquo;s tower.
Description Appearance Gelfondi is a horned devil, slightly shorter than usual. He was wearing some type or robes when the party surprised him in 2022-02-02 Import Campaign.</description></item><item><title>2022 01 19</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/19/2022-01-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/19/2022-01-19/</guid><description>Scaena et Tempore Summary The party desperately tries to dispatch the the two horned devils and subordinate in the main corridor before the devils can alert the guard barracks and the rest of the tower.</description></item><item><title>Belial</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/belial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/belial/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Belial Belial is the lord of Phlegethos, who jointly rules the fourth layer together with his daughter Fierna. This unusual partnership was allowed by Asmodeus as an exception to the usual requirement of one ruler per layer.</description></item><item><title>Fierna</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/fierna/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/fierna/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Fierna Daughter of Belial, with whom she co-rules Phlegethos.
Description Appearance Personality Described as fiery and even recklessly passionate.
Biography Key Info Relationships Quotations Trivia</description></item><item><title>Magrin</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magrin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/magrin/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Magrin A duergar who serves served as a chief manager of Tymphal&amp;rsquo;s operations.
Description Appearance Initial Meeting in the Torture Room at Fierna&amp;rsquo;s Tower a now frail and despondent duergar, heavily beaten and lacking teeth After Tymphal&amp;rsquo;s Punishment Magrin&amp;rsquo;s essence is now confined within a green steel shield.</description></item><item><title>Quilnorae</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/quilnorae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/quilnorae/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Quilnorae Reportedly an elvish paladin whose soul ended up in a Soul Coin in Fierna&amp;rsquo;s tower.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Aeortis issues a quest for Oneshoe to retrieve the coin with the soul of Quilnorae.</description></item><item><title>Zarinor</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zarinor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/zarinor/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Zarinor A white dragon, found bound in chains on the 42nd-floor during the Caper at Fierna&amp;rsquo;s Tower.
Description Appearance Large-sized, white dragon.
Personality Abnormally docile and intelligent for a smaller white dragon.</description></item><item><title>2022 01 05</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/05/2022-01-05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2022/01/05/2022-01-05/</guid><description>After the relative success last session stealthily clearing out the southeastern perimeter of the tower, the party initially follows a similar tactic: luring guards in small groups into the library to be dispatched quietly. Things go well at first. Then Val suddenly leaves the party to chat up a dragon, and when the group tries to follow, Zed gets the attention of a guardian hellhound, which alerts some of the more powerful devils in the tower.</description></item><item><title>2021 12 22</title><link>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/12/22/2021-12-22/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 23:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2021/12/22/2021-12-22/</guid><description>Oneshoe took point leading the party as they explored the first set of rooms along the perimeter of the tower going from Southwest corner counterclockwise towards the East. They find some torture victims and survive the activation of a devious torture chamber themselves. One of the party&amp;rsquo;s targets has been found. No sign of Magrin yet.</description></item></channel></rss>