<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nyx on tlake.io</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/nyx/</link><description>Recent content in Nyx on tlake.io</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Tanner Lake</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 03:35:25 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tlake.io/dnd/ref/characters/nyx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vision Quest</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-07-10/vision-quest/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-07-10/vision-quest/</guid><description>After the shared experience of Lady Mayweather, the parties visions diverge to mostly unsettling ends. Gimble and Nyx need assistance recovering, and the party seeks guidance from Lady Tiandra.</description></item><item><title>Spring Break</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-06-26/spring-break/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-06-26/spring-break/</guid><description>Horns has an overnight adventure with the local druids, Gimble succeeds in getting a glimpse of Finn&amp;rsquo;s lost family, and an audience with Lady Tiandra leads the party to a vision quest.</description></item><item><title>Seasonal Destinations</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-05-22/seasonal-destinations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-05-22/seasonal-destinations/</guid><description>Willoughby flies the party to a quick stop near Summer before narrowly avoiding the Wild Hunt on the way towards the Spring Court. A mostly exhausted party pushes on and enters the domain of spring, finding lodging and a possible audience with the Spring Court.</description></item><item><title>Go Shawty</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-03-20/go-shawty/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-03-20/go-shawty/</guid><description>The party is whisked away to celebrate a birthday with a DJ who doesn&amp;rsquo;t take No for an answer.</description></item><item><title>New Nyx, Who Dis?</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-02-21/new-nyx-who-dis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-02-21/new-nyx-who-dis/</guid><description>Horns magically restores Nyx, but she awakens without memory of the party or the last several years. This Nyx claims to be a young orphan fleeing from Mirea. The group stops for shelter, Gimble receives divination from a troubling source, and an envoy brings a message and gift for Finn.</description></item><item><title>Frozen</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-02-07/frozen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-02-07/frozen/</guid><description>The party finds itself back in the Feywild, much changed. Winter reigns. Nyx remains unresponsive. A frigid night brings visions. Gray recounts the danger of the Wild Hunt. Hoping for options, the group heads towards a fey crossing and reaches out to friends for answers.</description></item><item><title>Scattered Away</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-01-24/scattered-away/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-01-24/scattered-away/</guid><description>Timber proves to be a powerful foe, and a panicked Nyx sets up a desperate escape. Zed hangs back long enough to flirt with Mountain, and Bullwinkle heroically buys the party some time.</description></item><item><title>Timber Strikes</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-01-10/timber-strikes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2024-01-10/timber-strikes/</guid><description>Nyx has been found, and the party tries to convince her to fight back against her pursuers. Alone, Gray observes a familiar figure closing in on its prey. Nyx panics and pleads for escape, and Timber strikes. And he is not alone.</description></item><item><title>Flying into the Night</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/11/08/flying-into-the-night/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/11/08/flying-into-the-night/</guid><description>With portents that Nyx may be in danger, Gimble plans to leave Candlekeep. Before they leave, Val receives an intriguing quest from the Head Reader, and Cassandra Belacourt gives the party a faster means to travel towards Nyx&amp;rsquo;s likely location. The party briefly pass through Silverymoon before attempting to track down a hidden Nxy before they are too late.</description></item><item><title>The Walk Without Shame</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/30/the-walk-without-shame/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/30/the-walk-without-shame/</guid><description>The party continues processing the results of their research requests, an unsteady Gimble has some troubling revelations at the Temple of Oghma, and Oneshoe enthusiastically takes one for the team. Just as the party considers leaving to find Nyx, they are granted access to The Emerald Door and the interior of Candlekeep.</description></item><item><title>Research Obstructing Research</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/02/research-obstructing-research/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/08/02/research-obstructing-research/</guid><description>Gimble&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em>contact other plane&lt;/em> goes a little off the rails, and he has a conversation with Gruumsh. The group try to come up with a new plan for dealing with Nyx&amp;rsquo;s pursuers, since their charade in Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate failed to pull them off of Nyx&amp;rsquo;s trail. Val tours the Court of Air looking for any possible way to get past the Emerald Door. Cassandra visits, and the first round of requested knowledge is delievered.</description></item><item><title>Arrival in Candlekeep</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/06/21/arrival-in-candlekeep/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/06/21/arrival-in-candlekeep/</guid><description>The party gains entry into Candlekeep and its outer Court of Air, but they are barred investigating the inner library themselves, despite Gimble&amp;rsquo;s insistence. Instead, they fill out numerous research requests and seek lodging to rest and prepare for what comes next.</description></item><item><title>Can I Get a Receipt?</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/06/07/can-i-get-a-receipt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/06/07/can-i-get-a-receipt/</guid><description>Gimble fails to scry upon his pursuer, yet the party pushes on and teleports to Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate, where they make some noise about researching The Shard of Mystra. Horns enhances his wildshape ability, and Zed continues to evangelize the way of yoga. After the brief stop, they &lt;em>wind walk&lt;/em> the remainder of their journey, alighting just outside the fortress of Candlekeep.</description></item><item><title>A Study in Synthwave</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2023/05/24/a-study-in-synthwave/</guid><description>Psithyron displays his latest masterpiece. Gray opens up more about his family. A desperate message from Finn is foreseen, and a gnome returns. The party considers their options, and a bold, but likely foolish plan is made.</description></item><item><title>Nyx</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/nyx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/npcs/nyx/</guid><description>Import Campaign Characters
Nyx Gimble&amp;rsquo;s older sister, a rock gnome who is also gifted in Divination.
Description Appearance Personality Biography Key Info Growing up, Gimble was told he was an only child.</description></item><item><title>catch-22 items</title><link>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/09/05/catch-22-items/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 23:22:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tlake.io/dnd/posts/2020/09/05/catch-22-items/</guid><description>The Menagerie make several purchases from &lt;em>Grundle &amp;amp; Chode&amp;rsquo;s Arcane Boutique,&lt;/em> including a retainer for druids who like talking while wild-shaped. Gimble reaches a breaking point and leaves the party.</description></item></channel></rss>